

Phattanothai Pukham

Software Developer

Personal Information

| ≅ Nick Name | Fluke |
|--------------------------|-------------|
| ♣ Military Status | Reservist |
| Date of Availaility | Immediately |

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

| □ Tel | 0635957755 |
|------------------|--------------------------------|
| 5 Email | phattanothai.pukham@gmail.com |
| Address | 96 Moo.6 Tambon |
| | Thanthong, Amphur Phan, |
| | Chiang Rai 57250 |
| G Github | https://github.com/phattanotai |
| ■ Website | https://phattanothai-pukham- |
| | web.netlify.app |

Skills

| Graphic | Design | |
|---------|-----------|--|
| Fair | | |
| UX/UI [|)esign | |
| Fair | | |
| Coding | | |
| | Fluent | |
| Databas | se se | |
| | Good | |
| Server | | |
| | Standard | |
| Researc | h | |
| | Excellent | |

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2022 - Present Freelance Part-Time Software Developer

(Web App, Mobile App, REST API)

1 Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2022 Full Stack Developer Full-Time (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API) at OTEN INNOVATION, (Remote Work)

1 Sep. 2020 - 1 Nov. 2020 Freelance Software Developer (Web App,

REST API, LINE Bot) at Chiang Rai

1 Jun. 2019 - 31 Aug. 2020 Programmer Full-Time (Web App, Mobile App,

tcp server, REST API) at World Gps Tracker

Co.,Ltd, Chiang Rai http://wgtgps.net/login

1 May 2017 – 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

E ABILITIES

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, React Native, Ionic, Jquery Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design

DevExtreme, Rxjs, Redux, Vuex

One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Polling, Server Sent Event, Websocket, SocketIO

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet send sms email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Load Balance, Cluster Mode,

Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kong Api Gateway, GCP,

AWS

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack,

CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana,

gRPC, RabbitMQ

Research Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache

Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, Swift, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM